=As Promised=
(Adapted from "The Villain's Guide to Love",
a story on Zhihu Yanyan)
=Episode 3=
Then neither of us gets what we want.
Let's start over!
Don't you dare!
♪One thought of youth, laughing side
by side, I made a promise with you♪
♪One wish left unfulfilled, so close,
yet no words can be spoken♪
♪Leaving one soul alone, looking back
again between heaven and earth♪
♪How should I remember?
How should I say goodbye?♪
Why would you...
♪One thought waits for the snow,
shining bright in my memories♪
He Xiaoyuan.
Do you think dying will set you free?
For the past thirty-three lifetimes,
why did your parents die so young?
It was because
you were only the daughter
of an obscure minor official.
Did any of those renowned physicians
from the Imperial Medical Service
ever treat your parents?
(Imperial Medical Service)
Imperial Physician, please save them.
- Please save my parents.
- There's really nothing I can do.
I'm begging you.
Stop begging me.
Please.
There's really nothing I can do.
What if I kneel before you?
(Tomb of My Late Father, He Jingchuan)
♪Shining bright in my memories♪
Mother.
♪With no regrets for this chapter♪
♪Someday, when we meet again♪
As long as
you become the Crown Princess,
those renowned physicians
will kneel before you,
begging to treat your parents.
You'll have an endless supply
of rare medicinal herbs.
Death
is an escape for the weak.
But power
is the foundation of survival.
Promise me.
You must stay alive.
I promise.
Say it again.
I
promise Your Highness
that I will
become the Crown Princess.
♪Can I still hope that someday♪
♪We'll meet again?♪
Remember what you said today.
Return to the palace.
(That ruthless monster)
(actually risked his own life)
(to save me)
(back there.)
(Qingyan Palace)
All right.
This is what you've accomplished
after half a month of studying?
I refuse to believe
that drawing eyebrows
is harder than ruling a kingdom.
A little higher. Yes.
You...
Take a look.
I think it's all right.
What's wrong?
It's so ugly I could cry.
No...
Fu Yang.
Go to the market and find me
the Beauty Illustrated Guide,
and
the Makeup Manual.
Bring them all back
to me.
Well...
Later,
I'll
do a better job.
(Crescent Brows)
Mandarin Duck Brows.
(Mandarin Duck Brows)
Crescent Brows.
(I'm so hungry.)
(I miss Father's chicken soup,)
(Mother's pork ribs...)
(It's almost dark.)
(How much longer
is His Highness going to study?)
I've got it.
Come here.
♪I still remember
the fragrance of Lingnan lychees♪
♪The uneven stone steps,
mottled and damp with morning dew♪
♪Amid the bustling streets,
life was warm and full♪
♪I wished only for a simple,
contented life♪
♪One lamp saw us through the seasons,
never feeling the hardship♪
(What's going on?)
(When this murderous monster)
(isn't out to kill anyone,)
(he actually)
(looks rather handsome.)
♪But a document signed
by mistake sent you far away♪
♪The pounding hooves
faded too quickly to stop♪
♪I swallowed my tears,
not daring to speak♪
♪The Lingnan mist
chilled our old home through♪
♪Since we parted, our hearts
have gone separate ways♪
♪The palace crushed♪
♪A true heart and made it a wager♪
♪The crescent moon mourns
a noble heart given in vain♪
♪The land remains unchanged, but beneath
Chang'an's walls, loneliness endures♪
♪When you return,
the kapok flowers will bloom♪
Look.
♪And tell of our longing♪
Is that really me?
Well, Silly He?
I'm pretty good at this, aren't I?
(First trial run.)
(He Xiaoyuan,)
(you'd better not let me down.)
(All you have to do
is catch the Crown Prince's eye.)
(He Xiaoyuan,)
(you can do this.)
This ink is rather unusual.
♪My longing has nowhere to rest♪
♪Through the storm, I drift and sway♪
♪You are the prayer I hold in my palm♪
♪In one frozen moment,
my tears come into focus♪
♪My heart has long known♪
♪We made a promise long ago♪
♪To stay together until the end of time♪
♪You are the fate I cannot escape♪
♪How much must I let go♪
♪For one moment♪
♪To hold each other close♪
♪Would that be enough?♪